Jun22012|0110AM
RANUGAL
Chelyabinsk Province - Rusia
WARNING!
Military Zone.
Closed Area.
(Shooting prohibited!)
- Can we go faster?
- Not on these fucking roads.
Where are you from?
You're not a local.
I'm paying you to drive, not to chat.
- How much longer?
- Just over those hills.
Crap.
Dimitri, what did you bring us today?
My brothers, it's the same old thing.
It's been a slow season.
Get out of the truck, Dimitri.
Come on!
- Who is he?
- He's my cousin, Lev.
Why haven't you
mentioned him before?
Let's see what
you have in the back.
You Stay... in the truck.
Hands still!
Move on, Dimitri.
Alright.
Relax.
Keep moving!
Open it!
Come on, Dimitri.
Come on!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Who are you guys?
- What's he saying?
- He wants to know who we are.
- We're fucking salesmen.
- Better keep moving.
- I'm done. You didn't tell me.
- Listen sweetie.
Either you get behind the whell, or i do.
If you do, maybe you'll get your truck back.
- Get it?
- Got it.
Good man. Let's move it!
ALPHA
TOM CLANCYS GHOST RECON
Sub by: Ranugal
Sir.
Bring it in boys.
The military base was
decommissioned last year,
but Sokolov is still the CEO.
They're in two sets of
blocking positions. Here and here.
OK...
That's our "Boy".
Wait a minute.
There were three SUV's.
Advance party is clearing,
Shevchenko is hanging back.
- I got security, 30K you're on me?
- Yes sir.
- Pepper, I need you up top.
- Roger that.
- Chuck.
- Roger, spotting Pep.
Let's move!
Shevchenko won't be far behind.
Target_1: Autopilot
Come on! Come on! Faster.
Heads up, Sokolov is in the house.
Roger that, keep moving.
Target inbound, 30 seconds.
Copy.
- Is this Boris?
- Yes.
Come on, bring it over.
- You're on.
- Go!
Freeze.
OK.
Go!
Clear to engage.
"Scout" inbound.
Sick'em boy.
OK. Talk to me!
- You got eyes on Sokolov?
- Check.
- Shevchenko?
- Negative.
What the hell is that?
I don't know what
the hell they're doing.
Where is he?
- He's coming.
- He's coming?
Tangiers
worked out very well for us.
Everyone thinks,
it was the government.
No one trusts anyone anymore.
My assets are in place,
I need the package.
- He's coming.
- Is he coming or not?
- Yes!
- That's it. The deal is off!
Understand?
Cancel it! Take it back!
Take it back all!
Wait, Wait you!
The city has already been chosen.
You have ten minutes before
we clean the entire area.
- Get what I want.
- I always do.
- On target.
- Holding... holding.
Chuck? What you got?
Positive.
On Shevchenko.
- Fuck it.
- No shot.
Show me my money.
Here is...your money.
You can buy an army, general.
I already have an army.
Open it.
- Shit!
- Oh man!
- Cut "Scout's" mic!
- Cut it now!
Something's down there.
I've got acoustic interference,
there's something, jamming
the whole signal source.
It's as strong as hell whatever it is.
Let "Scout" take a peek.
Here we go.
Holy shit.
We've got a "Bulava" war-head.
Six heads, 150 kilotons a piece.
We got a loose fuckin' nuke.
WARNING!
Arm of Charge
Yes__No
OK, let's get it on.
OK, we have a deal.
Traitor!
Get the car!
- We got them both.
- We're out of here!
Stay put. Neutralize the area,
we've gotta get to that weapon.
- Two in the SUV.
- Your call.
Shit.
All right. We've gonna secure that Nuke.
- Chuck, can you neutralize that fuckin' thing?
- We're gonna find out.
Moving in.
Hey, you! Drop your weapon!
Drop the weapon!
- Get out!
- Don't shoot!
Pepper, keep an
eye on the North gate.
Ssshit!
- You ever done this before?
- Sure,
that was an American nuke,
and it was a simulator.
Everybody, everybody! Get together!
On your knees.
- OK!
- Who else?
Who else didn't come out?
There's something out there.
Get back!
Holly shit!
What the fuck... is that?
We got to get this
thing, stay away from the nuke.
- Chuck.
- Yes...
- ...and this is the honey pot!
- The PU-239!
- What?
- That's one...
five more to go.
I got nine, ten... inbound.
Cloaked and loaded.
They got flankers!
- Stay on that weapon. Pepper, cover him.
- Roger that.
Menu->>Scan->>Scanning:
Unknown...
Shit!
This thing is slow,
once it clocks you, head south.
- Four to go!
- Hey, Boss!
This thing ain't so slow!
Reloading!
- 30K! Get that thing to the canal!
- I'm trying!
Where the fuck are you, Chief?
God damn it! Where are you?
- How much longer god damn it!
- Two left.
Chuck is down.
- What?
- Chuck is down.
- You know what to do.
- Fuck!
Sorry Pal!
Engine->>Weapon->>Scan
->>Search program
I'm at the rendez-vous point.
We got them all!
TO BE CONTINUED
->>RanuGal
Subscene.com